roommatesdecor.com 2018-05-10

# Privacy Policy | RoomMates

Thank you for visiting the RoomMates website! This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected by this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information to us.

By using our website, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted; changes will only apply to activities and information going forward, not on a retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review our privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Please note that the privacy practices described here are for this website only. If you visit other websites, including those linked by RoomMates, please review their policy to understand how personal information is used by their website.

We collect personally identifiable information (ex. names, addresses, email addresses, etc.) when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information provided is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request unless you give us permission to use it in another manner (ex. to sign you up to receive our newsletter or special offers).

Our site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering technical information (ex. browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors) and understanding how visitors use our site. Cookies can also help customize the website for visitors. Personal information _cannot_ be collected via cookies and other tracking technology. However, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when permitted or required by law, when trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions, or when investigating fraud which has already taken place. Information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information.

All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. RoomMates abides by the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy at our discretion or when required by law. Any changes to this policy will be posted.

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy or how we use your personal information, you can contact us at any time at [info@roommatesdecor.com](mailto:info@roommatesdecor.com) or by calling (800) 236-4520 (8 AM to 6 PM EST, M-F).

Thank you for reading!
